[ Pause ]
Only on those two pages he repeated that.
There was no place else.
One time I was listening.
Yes.
You want some?
I didn't say that.
No, no.
There's no desire.
But you know, I knew.
Because I think also it's not entirely related.
There's so many other people.
[ Inaudible ]
(speaking in foreign language)
You know, what his dirty is done.
He never said that.
[NON-ENGLISH SPEECH]
And no, if you'd like to put a promise right into it, say the whole government is ready to get out.
It's important being that, you need to be more present when you're conscious.
Well, that's important.
You're right.
There's also the Congress, the old Congress.
It's not a right world.
Because we both need to understand the Congress, but he got it.
Even the number of something came.
[ Inaudible ]
I'm only one port of the book.
He will understand about four pages of the Italian.
And then, we will get a picture of things we did at the moment.
The picture of Jania, Jania, Jania.
And then, we will get a picture of Maré, Jania.
It is a couple of years ago.
You want to get confused with it?
Oh, very confused.
You want to get confused?
I think you have to look confused, and if you can't try the sentence,
then I'll get a picture.
Then you got some law at that time.
Because he's a bit of reason,
and I see him, he's lying.
No, he didn't know.
No.
He's just a thousand more.
You got it?
I just met him about to.
Wait a minute.
The disc I met.
No, you did.
Yeah, I forgot.
I should not.
If I remember, there was a mess.
No, it's not a mess, you forgot.
Yeah, exactly.
I think it's very important. I think that's the whole thing.
The time we gave was one.
You know, that dude that has your two.
This person says, "Did you survive, you got him?"
Like 19.
And that is going to be the foundation.
It has gone with one.
You got it. I'm going with you.
Is that right? How would I change the foundation?
Right.
It's because of the entire world.
It is.
[ Inaudible ]
>> Yes.
>> I often have an article in music, but the Kenberg Journal,
of course, that's actually most American,
and there's a working series.
So they're applied in the Egyptian press.
And I have to write the question,
the beginning of the madness. The number of night in the circuit, the mosquito we've planted, the birds in the office, the layup was on the altar, and the preserve was the purpose of the screen.
But this means all you want to do is, this is why it is, invaded to the Arab people. Divine can never entirely be saved to Quran against you.
The difference between the people of the United States is that it is the source of the world. However, the people of the competition, the date of the birth of the founder, even that is very bad.
Because the use of the English is the English in India here, which is abroad. But in other words, if people use this for their own care, it's more argument than me.
But it's very clear, this woman is a disability.
The violence to the people of my appeal to be
a total number because of the American violence of whites.
But all this is working.
All these are working. All these are working.
All these are going to be the police. It's entirely the violence.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
(speaking in foreign language)
- No, I was here.
- Yeah, I was here in the year,
1970, 1970.
(speaking in foreign language)
- Yeah.
- So did you like it?
Very much that I...
Some people were nice to me, others were not nice.
You mean that you were walking away from saying it to me?
You think for people, you need papermen of life.
But you need to search in a company to go to the forest.
You're giving me a card. You're giving me a card downtown.
So they give me a card downtown?
What about the right man, shoot out?
No, this was in town of Malice, Malice.
- Malice. - That's it.
- That's it. - That's it.
They gave me a car, they gave me a hotel.
But they were not allowed me to go to Mossegane.
So I refused because I refused to hotel
and I went to sleep in dinner on the concert.
- Would you...
- Would you be there? - Yeah.
- Girl, would you be there in a bar of children? - No.
- Ah, how much? - I'm a little laggily.
- You can be. - But do you want to be there?
They don't talk about him at all. I've got to hear about him more here than I do.
So they wrote a book about him.
They wrote a book.
I was going to say it to the 20th century.
Yeah.
And I wrote a book.
In fact, I keep quoting one of him, quote me.
And it's not a gentleman.
Especially when they don't come to me,
they don't know anything about him.
Do you have to go to here?
No, I don't have to.
We have something in the building.
Somewhere, but it's a tiny, required of post.
[inaudible]
(inaudible)
I'm gonna be a student in a minute and I thought that. I'm gonna be like her.
How many people are not saying anything? I thought. And I was just kind of a student.
And I hope everything works out. I'm really worried.
Yeah. I can't believe it. I can't believe it. I've just talked to one of you.
I was in both the research from one center from around four years and then it was this side of the project for two years. It was good that it was a sign for the project for two years. And then there was a sign for the mission. Can I have your borrows for a copy of this? I'm sorry. No, I don't have a dime. Sure. I'm trying to get as much material as I can out these redness files.
I don't think he's a good man.
What do you think about this?
The President has a dictator in the last of them.
He's now trapped in the keeping of drugs.
[ Inaudible ]
I don't think so.
He has some habits that he hears from his father, he cries,
five times a day, and he talks about the plan, but he doesn't.
He doesn't.
He's opposed to the hurry.
I thought he said...
Only, but I only have four apologies.
He had this statement,
(speaking in foreign language)
- You had the statement in billboards throughout the country.
And then after making it the motto of the nation,
(speaking in foreign language)
or everything throughout the country,
then he discovered it was not a hadith.
(speaking in foreign language)
This term is "lambered ha-diz-ri"
and then he discovers not a ha-diz-ri
or somebody told him not a ha-diz.
He was wearing man and he...
What was the thing in the world?
He said, "Beware of the one that you're good to."
I thought he was a folk or ha-diz in general.
We are after this.
Then he calls him and says, "Whom who says this is a ha-diz?"
And then he tells us about ha-diz and the contradiction of ha-diz.
And then he says, "Well, this is my man."
Maybe you made it to trouble yourself at that point.
Well, he was, but there wasn't a lot in your mind.
You made it to trouble yourself at a certain point, too.
But at the time, when you accepted happiness,
and then you made it to trouble about it.
I mean, for some of us, we'd call a couple of wounds on from outside.
This is the beginning, right here. I wrote an article here.
But you know, he's trying to change the sense.
The point.
The beginning.
Change.
(speaking in foreign language)
- That's more academic, it's not.
before. Yeah, but really you know the war's concerned that they're doing something. So I should listen to why when I hear about things about all these leaders in the Middle East, I wonder how much of it is propaganda.
A lot of it. You know because the propaganda machines are very active and we get things here sifted down from many mayors and you can only judge the man in the industry with those people by their writings about what they've done.
So I'm not going to be so fast as young teacher.
And for what I am, you know, I hear what's going on for people
saying you can't buy vegetables now in Libya.
I don't live in India.
I think you cannot buy vegetables now here in Libya.
And then, you know, I think a lot of stuff.
And I'm going to keep my reserve my judgment about Qaddafi
until I have studied more about his brother,
written in--
and not negated in the--
because all he's written, I could very attracted to what he--
he takes a system series methodology,
what we call a general opposed to--
But did you ask the people to let him love it?
I think it would be much.
Also very helpful to you.
You can miss the video.
I would not voice it.
I would like to.
His writing is already written.
What he's doing is terrible.
I haven't been done some of my...
What is the deal?
I haven't been done like...
and living people are not very happy.
You can live in a big prison.
(distant chattering)